Finding aid for the William Bast papers LSC.2290
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Television productions, 1960-2001
  - Perry Mason (CBS, 1957-1965)
    - Teleplay "The Case of the Fatal Fortune", June 9, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Includes outline by Arthur Hoffe.
    - Teleplay "The Case of the Impetuous Imp", August 10, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Teleplay "The Case of the Silent Six", October 5, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Teleplay "The Case of the Silent Six", October 11, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Teleplay "The Case of the Crafty Kidnapper", March 28, 1966; Significant insect damage. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Power and Beauty (Showtime, 2002)
    - Revised first draft story outline "Judith Exner"by William Bast & Paul Huson, September 19, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Treatment "The Judith Exner Story" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], March 8, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Third draft teleplay "Promises to Keep: The Judith Exner Story" by William Bast & Paul Huson, February 11, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Third draft teleplay "Promises to Keep: The Judith Exner Story" by William Bast & Paul Huson, November 2, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Unpaginated rough third draft "Promises to Keep: The Judith Exner Story" [annotated], undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Final shooting script "Beauty & Power" by David Erickson, March 29, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ABC notes, 1993-1995 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Includes script notes; transcripts of an interview between producer Tracey Alexander and Judith Exner.
    - Agreements, 1990-1998 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Audio cassettes, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      FILE CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this folder will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials, you must notify the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk in advance of your visit.
      Contains five tapes, possibly with interviews with Judith Exner.
    - NBC versions, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      Contains notes and outlines.
    - Notes, 1990-1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Includes lists of questions for Judith Exner.
    - Notes and correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Includes letter from Judith Exner objecting to the portrayal of her in a treatment.
    - Research, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Script notes, 1994-2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Writers Guild of America, 1995-2001 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Includes material regarding credit arbitration.
  - The Rogues (NBC, 1964-1965)
    - Teleplay "Bow to a Master", November 30, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Includes annotated outlines.
  - The Scarlet Pimpernel (CBS, 1982)
    - Treatment by David Conroy, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Summaries [annotated], undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Treatment, July 20, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Treatments [annotated], July 20, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Teleplay [annotated], November 9, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Teleplay, November 23, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Teleplay "Part One", December 1, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Teleplay "Part Two", December 1, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Second draft teleplay [annotated], March 16, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay, March 16, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Revised second draft teleplay, April 22, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Final revised shooting script, May 20, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Revised second draft teleplay, May 20, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Revised second draft teleplay [annotated], May 20, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Revised second draft teleplay [annotated], May 20, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Final revised shooting script [annotated], May 20, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Deleted pages [annotated], April 22, 1982-June 3, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Revised second draft teleplay, May 20, 1982-June 24, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Revised second draft teleplay, May 20, 1982-July 19, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Revised pages, June 14, 1982-July 19, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      Includes letter from producer David Conroy.
    - Agreements, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Conroy, David, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      Includes script notes.
    - Notes on index cards, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Novel [annotated], 1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      Contains The Scarlet Pimpernel by Baroness Orczy (New York: Signet) [photocopy].
    - Novel [annotated], undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
      Contains novel Eldorado [photocopy].
    - Publicity, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Includes: clippings; reviews; letter notifying William Bast that he would receive a Christopher Award.
  - Secrets (NBC, 1992)
    - Story outlines "Danielle Steel's Secrets" by William Bast and Paul Huson, August 5, 1981-August 8, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - First draft teleplay "Danielle Steel's Secrets" by William Bast and Paul Huson, September 19, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Danielle Steel's Secrets" by William Bast and Paul Huson, October 14, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Danielle Steel's Secrets" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], October 16, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Danielle Steel's Secrets" by William Bast and Paul Huson, November 14, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Final draft teleplay "Danielle Steel's Secrets" by Bill Bast & Paul Huson and L. Virginia Browne, January 13, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      Includes material on credit arbitration.
    - Notes and reviews, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Includes script notes from Danielle Steel and director Peter Hunt.
  - The Star Maker (NBC, 1981)
    - Teleplay "Part One" [annotated], July 15, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Teleplay "Part One" [annotated], July 15, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Revised teleplay "Part One: Dawn" [annotated], July 15, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Teleplay "Part Two" [annotated], September 8, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Combined teleplay, July 15, 1980-September 8, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Teleplay "Part Two", September 8, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Second draft teleplay "Part One: Dawn", November 3, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Second draft teleplay "Part Two: Angel", November 3, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Revised draft "Part I: Dawn" [annotated], January 12, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Revised draft "Part Two: Angel" [annotated], January 12, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Shooting script "Part I: Dawn", January 12, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Shooting script "Part Two: Angel", January 12, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Revised shooting script "Part I: Dawn", January 28, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Revised shooting script "Part I: Dawn", January 28, 1981-January 30, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Revised shooting script "Part Two: Angel", January 31, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Master script [David Debin's version], January 28, 1981-January 31, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Final revised shooting script "Part I: Dawn", March 27, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Final revised shooting script "Part Two: Angel", March 27, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Production file, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Includes cast list; shooting schedules; script notes.
    - Publicity, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Research, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Contains clippings about John and Bo Derek and Roman Polanski.
  - The Survivors (ABC, 1969-1970)
    - Teleplay "Chapter Nine" by William Bast from a story by John Wilder, September 3, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Thirty-Minute Theatre (BBC, 1965-1973)
    - Rough draft teleplay "Boa Constrictor" [annotated], undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - First draft teleplay "Boa Constrictor" [annotated], March 20, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Rehearsal script "Boa Constrictor", April 17, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Rehearsal script "Boa Constrictor" [annotated], April 17, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Rehearsal script "Boa Constrictor" [annotated], April 17, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Rehearsal script "Boa Constrictor" [annotated], April 17, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Camera script "Boa Constrictor", April 26, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Includes reviews; clippings about protests against the existence of gay characters on television and the Black and White Minstrel Show.
  - Tom's Christmas Tree (2006)
    - Script by Robert Worley and Graham Churchyard, July 11, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence and notes [William Bast and Paul Huson were in negotiations to do rewrites, but their fee was too high].
  - Tucker's Witch (CBS, 1982-1983)
    Scripts are listed according to broadcast order.
    - Story outlines "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], October 31, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], December 1, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - First draft pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, December 1, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Revised first draft pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, December 9, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Revised first draft pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], December 9, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Revised first draft pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, December 14, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Final draft pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], December 18, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Second draft pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, December 23, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Second draft pilot script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], December 23, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous teleplay pages "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" [annotated], undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, January 18, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Revised shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, February 1, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Revised shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], February 1, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Contains four differently-annotated copies.
    - Final shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, February 18, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Final shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], February 18, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      Contains three differently-annotated copies.
    - Final shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, February 18, 1982-March 2, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      Includes production memos.
    - Final shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson, July 22, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Final shooting script "The Good Witch of Laurel Canyon" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], July 22, 1982-July 26, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - First draft teleplay "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], July 8, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Teleplay "Big Mouth" [no writer credited; annotated], undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Second draft teleplay "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], July 15, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Second revised draft teleplay "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson, July 19, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Second revised draft teleplay "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], July 19, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      Includes notes from the network and Philip Mandelker.
    - Second revised draft teleplay "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson, July 28, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Final shooting script "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], August 4, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Final shooting script "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson, August 5, 1982-August 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Final shooting script "Big Mouth" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], August 5, 1982-August 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Second draft teleplay "The Corpse Who Knew Too Much" by Steve Kline [annotated], July 16, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "The Corpse Who Knew Too Much" by Steve Kline [annotated], August 2, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Final draft teleplay "The Corpse Who Knew Too Much" by Steve Kline, August 9, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "The Toltec Death Mask" by MaryAnne Kasica & Michael Scheff, September 1, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Final draft teleplay "The Toltec Death Mask" by MaryAnne Kasica & Michael Scheff, September 9, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Revised shooting script "Terminal Case" by Lee Sheldon, September 20, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Final draft teleplay "Abra Cadaver" by Bernie Kukoff, August 20, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Final draft teleplay "Abra Cadaver" by Bernie Kukoff, August 20, 1982-August 27, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Shooting script "Dye Job" by Marc Rubin, October 20, 1982-October 28, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Shooting script "Psych Out" by Steve Kline, October 11, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Shooting script "Rock Is a Hard Place" by Lee Sheldon, October 28, 1982-November 10, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - First draft teleplay "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], September 10, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - First draft teleplay "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson, September 10, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Second draft teleplay "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson, September 22, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], September 24, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], September 29, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], September 30, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Shooting script "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], October 2, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Shooting script "Formula for Revenge" by William Bast and Paul Huson, October 2, 1982-October 7, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Shooting script "Living and Presumed Dead" by Steve Kline, November 18, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Revised shooting script "Living and Presumed Dead" by Steve Kline, November 22, 1982-November 29, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Revised shooting script "Murder Is the Key" by Bernie Kukoff, November 11, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Revised shooting script "Murder Is the Key" by Bernie Kukoff, November 11, 1982-November 19, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Agreements, 1982-1984 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - "Bull sessions", undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Contains transcript of a story conference.
    - Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Development, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Contains material regarding the premise of the series and potential storylines; a note about Great Expectations dating service lists the contact there as "Bryan Cranston."
    - Legal, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Contains material regarding inaccuracies in a New York Times article on the cancellation of the series.
    - Production, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Includes staff and crew lists; schedules; correspondence.
    - Research, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Story ideas, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      Contains unproduced outlines and treatments; writers include Brian Clemens & Dennis Spooner, Robert Sheehan, Larry Forrester, Duane Poole & Tom Swale, MaryAnne Kasica & Michael Scheff, Lee Sheldon, William Bast & Paul Huson.
  - Twist of Fate (NBC, 1989)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Teleplay "Pursuit Part One" [no writers credited] [annotated], undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Teleplay "Pursuit Part One" [no writers credited] [annotated], March 19, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by Wiiliam Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], March 26, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast & Paul Huson, April 14, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], April 29, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], April 29, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by Wiiliam Bast & Paul Huson, May 1, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], May 1, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast & Paul Huson, May 1, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], May, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], May, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 12, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 12, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], May 12, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      Contains two differently-annotated copies.
    - Revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], May 15, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" [no writers credited] [annotated], May 15, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 18, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], May 18, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 18, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], May 18, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Second draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Second draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast & Paul Huson, June 17, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Second draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast, Paul Huson [annotated], June 17, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Second draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast & Paul Huson, June 24, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], June 24, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by Gy Waldron, December 29, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - First draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by Gy Waldron, February 25, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], May 5, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron, with revisions by Larry White, May 5, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], May 5, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron, with revisions by Larry White, May 5, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Producer's revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], May 5, 1988-August 4, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Producer's revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by Wiiliam Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], May 5, 1988-August 4, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Producer's revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], May 5, 1988-August 4, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Producer's revised draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], May 5, 1988-August 4, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Final draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], August 10, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Final draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by Wiiliam Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron, August 10, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Final draft teleplay "Pursuit Part One" by William Bast & Paul Huson, August 10, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Final draft teleplay "Part One" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], August 10, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Final draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron, August 15, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Final draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], August 15, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Final draft teleplay "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], August 15, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Final shooting draft "Pursuit Part Two" by William Bast, Paul Huson, and Gy Waldron [annotated], August 15, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Final draft teleplay "Part Two" by William Bast and Paul Huson, August 15, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1986-1990 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      Includes material regarding credit arbitration; distribution statements.
    - Novel, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
      Contains Pursuit by Robert L. Fish (London:Macdonald General Books) [two annotated photocopies].
    - Publicity, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Script notes, 1987-1988 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Video cassettes, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      FILE CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this file will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials, you must notify the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk in advance of your visit.
      Viewing copy on two VHS cassettes.
  - The Waltons (CBS, 1971-1981)
    - First draft teleplay "Last Stop: Walton's Mountain", October 5, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      Biographical / Historical
      Broadcast as "The Actress."
    - Revised final draft teleplay "The Actress", November 13, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Series 2. Feature film productions, 1967-1968
  - The Betsy (Allied Artists, 1978)
    - Revised screenplay by Walter Bernstein, December 27, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Revised screenplay by Walter Bernstein [annotated], December 27, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - First draft screenplay by Walter Bernstein [annotated], March 14, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - First draft screenplay [annotated], March 14, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Second draft screenplay [annotated], March 31, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Second draft screenplay [annotated], April 6, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Second draft screenplay, April 11, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Revised second draft screenplay [annotated], undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay, May 9, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 6)